そこに お通ししてちょうだい
Bring her in, please.
As you wish.
かしこまりました
渡辺早季さんね
Watanabe Saki-san, right?
瑞穂ちゃんのお嬢さんの
Mizuho-chan’s treasured little girl…
はいっ！
I am!
Don’t be so nervous.
そんなに
かしこまらなくていいのよ
FROM THE NEW WORLD
Episode Twelve
Weak Link
I’m Asahina Tomiko.
朝比奈 富子です
うちの覚が いつも
仲良くしていただいているそうね
I hear you’re good friends with Satoru.
覚とは…
覚さんとは ずっと幼なじみで
Satoru—
Satoru-san and I have been friends since we were little, and—
そう… 想像してたとおりね
I see.
Your eyes are just as wonderful as I’d imagined.
すごく いい目をしてるわ
光があるの
There is light in them.
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
I’ve always wanted to talk to you, you know?
私はね どうしても あなたと
一度お話をしてみたかったの
どうしてですか？
Why?
That’s because…
それはね あなたに いずれ
私の後を継いでもらいたいからよ
I want you to eventually succeed me.
Surprised?
驚いた？ でも 決して
I’m not joking, though.
思いつきで
言ってるんじゃないのよ
But… There is no way that I am fit for the role!
そんな… 私なんかに
務まるはずありません
アッハハ…
瑞穂ちゃんと同じこと言うのね
That’s exactly what Mizuho-chan said.
Do you know my mother?
母をご存じなんですか？
Yes, ever since she was born.
ええ 生まれた時からね
あのコには 人の上に立つ
すばらしい素質があるわ
She has a knack for making others follow her.
She’s doing an excellent job as librarian.
今も図書館司書として
申し分なくやっている
でも 私の職責には
さらに求められるものがあるの
However, my position requires more than that.
私なんて 成績も それほど…
My grades aren’t very good…
学校で試されるのは
呪力の素質だけじゃないのよ
Your Cantus isn’t all that is assessed in school.
もう 一つ
人格指数というものがあるの
There’s the personality index as well.
Personality index?
人格指数？
Yes.
そう いつの世も
指導者たちに求められてきたのは
That’s what has always been demanded of leaders.
この数値なのよ
人格指数っていうのは
どれだけ その人が
The personality index shows the mental stability of the person.
安定しているかっていうことを
示すものなの
どんな想定外の出来事があっても
自分を見失ったりせず
Can they remain themselves even when all takes an entirely unexpected turn?
一貫した自分を保てるか
指導者にとっては
いちばん大事なことなの
That’s the most important quality of a leader.
And my score is high?
それが 私は高かったんですか？
Yes, wonderfully high.
ええ すばらしい数値だったわ
全人学級が
始まって以来かもしれない
Maybe the best in the history of the Academy.
でも それだけじゃないわ
But that’s not all.
あなたの すごいのはね
全てを知ってからでも
Most remarkable is that even when you discovered the truth, there was no permanent decline in your score.
指数上は ほとんどダメージが
残らなかったということなの
全てって 何のことですか？
What are you referring to?
国立国会図書館つくば館
ミノシロモドキね
The Tsukuba branch of the National
Assembly Library—the false minoshiro.
あなたはミノシロモドキから
You learned about mankind’s bloodstained history from the false minoshiro.
人類の血塗られた歴史について
学んだ
そして私たちの社会が
どんなに薄氷を踏んで
You discovered how our society found peace and on what thin ice we tread.
今の平和と安定を手に入れたかを
知った
After you returned, we thoroughly examined you psychologically.
あなたたちが帰還してから
徹底的な心理テストを行い
経過観察をしたの
あなたの人格指数は激動の後
Your personality index stabilized
surprisingly quickly after the initial shock.
見事に短時間で回復したのよ
The others found their return to normal far more arduous.
他の４人は
かなりの長期間にわたって
ガタガタの状態だったわ
それ もしかして 最初から 全部
仕組まれてたことなんですか？
Did you plan it all from the beginning?
Hardly.
まさか いくらなんでも
そんな危険な賭けはしませんよ
We’d never take such a big risk.
あなたたちが
多少の規則違反を犯すのは
All we knew was that you were planning some sort of violation of the rules during summer camp.
最初から分かっていたことです
でも まさか 本当に
ミノシロモドキを捕まえるなんて
Who would’ve thought you would actually catch a false minoshiro?
誰にも想像できなかったわね
Are those test results why I am here?
でも そんなテストの結果だけで…
No.
いいえ 町の人全員の命運を
担っている最高責任者にはね
To be able to shoulder the fate of
all the people as its highest leader,
清濁併せ飲む度量
one needs to have a broad mind and nerves of steel .
真実を知っても動じない
胆力が必要なのよ
あなたには それがあるわ
You have those.
私たちは どうして
処分されなかったんですか？
Why were we not disposed of?
That’s not our jurisdiction, but the Board of Education’s.
それを決めているのは
私たちじゃないの
教育委員会
議長は宏美ちゃんね
Their chief is Hiromi-chan.
She’s always been worrying over nothing.
小さい頃から
とっても心配性のコだったわ
The Ethics Committee is the highest authority in the villages,
倫理委員会は
この町の最高意思決定機関だけど
教育委員会が
独自に決めたことには
but we don’t generally interfere with the Board of Education’s decisions.
基本的に口を挟まないできたの
Your cases were an exception.
でも あなたたちのことは例外
私からお願いして
処分を行わないようにしたの
I asked them not to dispose of you.
覚がいたからですか？
Was it because of Satoru?
No. I would never let personal sentiments get in the way of such important matters.
いいえ こんな重要な決定に
私情は挟みません
全ては あなたがいたからなのよ
You were the reason.
You are indispensable for the future of the villages.
あなたは この町の将来にとって
必要な人だから
Please don’t think badly of Hiromi-chan and her people.
だけど どうか宏美ちゃんたちを
悪く思わないでね
あの人たちは 一種の恐怖症に
突き動かされているだけなのよ
They’re driven by a sort of paranoia.
恐怖症？
Paranoia?
ううん 少し言葉が
悪かったかもしれないわね
Perhaps that was a bad choice of words.
I have the exact same fears too.
私自身 全く同じ恐怖を
持っているもの
同じ恐怖って何ですか？
Fears of what?
まあ 決まってるじゃないの
Isn’t that obvious?
私たちにとって
本当に恐ろしい存在は
There are only two things in this world we really have to fear.
この世で２つしかないでしょう？
悪鬼と… そして業魔よ
Fiends and Karma Demons.
But Hiromi-chan and her people have never seen a real Fiend or Karma Demon.
でも宏美ちゃんたちは 本物の
悪鬼や業魔を見たことはないわ
だから 私は あの人たちのは
単なる恐怖症だって
That’s why I’m always saying that
they’re simply driven by paranoia.
いつも言ってるの
So you have actually…
じゃあ 実際に…
Yes. I’ve seen them myself.
ええ 私は この目で見たわ
Up close and personal, I might add.
それも ごく間近で
聞きたい？
Want to hear about it?
はい
Yes.
悪鬼は これまでに全世界で
30近い症例が記録されているの
Records detail the exploits of close to 30 Fiends throughout the world.
All were boys except for two.
そのうち たった２例を除いて
全て男子だったのよ
とりあえず そのコのことは
Ｋと呼ぶことにしましょう
Let’s call this boy K.
何に見える？
What does this remind you of?
死んだ人
A corpse.
And this?
じゃあ 次は？
斧 割られてる
An axe. It’s broken.
次は？
犬 首がない
And this?
A dog. Beheaded.
The desire for destruction and bloodshed must have been deeply entrenched in his subconsciousness.
おそらく無意識の中では
破壊と殺戮に対する
欲求が渦巻いていたのね
残虐な連想ばかりでした
All his associations were violent.
非常に大きなストレスが
かかっているようですね
He must be under great stress.
至極 普通の生徒なのですが…
But he’s a completely average student…
この事例だけでは 何とも…
This data doesn’t allow much of a decision.
何か手を打つべきだと
思うのですが
I really think we should do something.
教育委員会に支持を仰ぎましょう
Let’s ask the Board of Education for directions.
As you wish.
お願いします
But nobody paid much heed to his abnormality at the time.
でも このときは
なぜか彼の異常性は
さほど重要視されなかった
その前の悪鬼の出現から
80年以上が経過していたこと
Reason One: Already 80 years had passed since the last appearance of a Fiend.
Reason Two: K’s mother was a rather
outspoken member of the main village council.
Ｋの母親が
当時うるさ型で知られる
町議会議員だったこと
Reason Three: No established mechanisms for such situations were in place at the time.
この時点では
取るべき有効な方策が
ほとんどなかったこと…
The combination of all these factors made it happen one day.
そんなことが積み重なり
ある日
とうとう事件は起こったのよ
キャ～！
誰一人として悪鬼に有効な反撃を
加えることはできなかった
No one could raise a hand against the rampaging Fiend.
全員 強固な攻撃抑制と
愧死機構によって
They were all bound by a powerful attack inhibition and their own death feedback.
腕を縛られていた
Attacking a fellow human being wasn’t possible.
つまり
対人攻撃は不可能だったからよ
Approximately one thousand died in Kamisu 66 that day.
この時 死んだ神栖66町の人々は
およそ1,000人
All at the hands of K.
たった１人のＫのために
どう？ まだ聞きたい？
Do you want to know more?
I’d like to know how K was stopped in the end.
どうやってＫを止めることが
できたのか 知りたいです
いいわ
Very well.
Fiends have no attack inhibition.
悪鬼には攻撃抑制がない
いつ相手から
攻撃を受けるかという
Some suggest that they attack and kill those around them preemptively, driven by their fear of being attacked.
恐怖に駆られて
周囲の人間を皆殺しにするまで
先制攻撃を
かけ続けるという説があるの
もう 一つ
悪鬼は脳内で分泌される
Another theory is that Fiends become
intoxicated by the endorphins in their brain,
快楽物質のために
酩酊したような状態になって
and simply cannot stop their slaughter.
大量殺人を
やめられなくなるらしくてね
別名を｢フォックス･イン･ザ･
ヘンハウス｣と呼ぶ由縁ね
That’s why the syndrome is also called “Fox in the Henhouse”.
先生！
どうした？
Doctor!
What’s wrong?
子供が…
The boy!
朝比奈君は
患者の手当てをしていなさい
Take care of the patients, Asahina-kun.
Examination room
薬
Medicine…
Do you think you’re sick?
どこか悪いのかい？
I caught a cold.
風邪をひいたんです
風邪か 喉を診てみよう
A cold, huh?
Let me look at your throat.
赤いな 腫れてる
It looks inflamed and swollen.
もう 一度 口を開けて
Open your mouth again.
抗生物質を持って来て
Bring him antibiotics.
Huh? Okay!
えっ？ はい！
This is cold medicine.
風邪薬だよ これと
ペニシリンを併用するんだ
It works well with penicillin.
Ｋは土田先生の頭を
吹き飛ばしていた
K blew off Dr. Tsuchida’s head.
そしてＫ自身
悪鬼も その薬で死んだの
Then he himself died from the drug.
It took much patience before the villages
grappled with the scars left by the Fiend.
町が悪鬼の残した爪痕から
立ち直るまでには
辛抱強い取り組みが必要だった
最初に私たちがやったことが
何だったか分かる？
Do you know what we did first?
We eliminated all who showed the potential to be like K.
Ｋのような可能性を持つ者を
完全に取り除くことよ
Potential… Eliminated?
可能性を… 取り除く？
誤解しないでほしいんだけど
これは復讐じゃないの
Please don’t misunderstand me.
It wasn’t revenge.
ただ２度と再び悪鬼の出現を
許してはならないという
We were simply determined to avert the appearance of another Fiend.
固い決意の表れだったの
でも どうやって その人たちを？
But how did you eliminate them?
At that time we used the queerats.
そのときはバケネズミを使ったの
We commanded the most powerful warriors of loyal colonies to attack them.
人間に忠実なコロニーから
精強な兵を選んで襲撃させたの
イチかバチかだったけど
It was an all-or-nothing strategy,
but luckily also a complete success.
まあ完璧な成功と
言っていいでしょうね
However, there was no guarantee that Fiends would never appear again.
だけど まだ 悪鬼が
現れないという保証はないから
So what did you do?
じゃあ どうしたんですか？
The former Code of Ethics considered a child to be
endowed with human rights 22 weeks after conception.
旧倫理規定では
人権が発生するのは
受胎後22週目からだった
In the new Code of Ethics, this was moved to their 17th birthday.
新しい倫理規定では これを
生後17歳まで後ろ倒しにしたの
Accordingly, the Board of Education was given the power to order their disposal until their 17th birthday.
したがって 17歳までは
教育委員会の職権において
処分が可能になったの
That’s crazy…
そんなの おかしい…
The method of disposal was likewise
changed to something more polished.
処分方法も ずっと
洗練されたやり方に変更されたわ
Tainted Cats were selectively bred using Cantus from ordinary household cats.
普通の家猫を呪力によって
品種改良し 不浄猫を作り出したの
その後は徹底した
取り組みによって
Thanks to these thorough measures that we undertook to remove potential Fiends,
危険な可能性は
全て事前に取り除いたために
悪鬼は 一度も現れていない
their appearances have since stopped.
だけど もう１つの
恐ろしい事件が起きたの
However, another terrifying incident occurred.
今から ほんの20年ほど前の
出来事なのよ
It has barely been twenty years since then.
呪力が漏出する危険性については
The potential risks of leaking Cantus were noted as early as the final years of the ancient civilization.
古代文明の末期から
指摘されていたらしいわ
でも悪い漏出
バッド･スピルという現象は
However, “bad spill”, the phenomenon of destructive leakage, was overlooked and underestimated for a long time.
長い間 見過ごされ
過小評価されてきた
周囲の物にゆがみが出るくらいで
It was thought that such changes to the environment would pose humans and other animals no harm.
人畜に危害が及ぶ危険性は
ないとされていたの
It was at that time that a girl,
Kutegawa Izumi, proved us wrong.
ところが その生徒 湫川泉美には
それが当てはまらなかったの
黄金の郷の外れにあった農場の
ひとり娘だったのだけれどね
She was an only child who lived on a farm outside the village of Gold.
彼女の呪力は周囲にあるもの
全てを汚染した
Her Cantus polluted everything around her.
倫理委員会と教育委員会は
専門家による
The Board of Education and Ethics Committee sent specialists to investigate.
特別調査班を立ち上げたわ
その結果 彼女のバッド･スピルが
Their investigation showed that the “bad spill” of her Cantus could damage even human DNA.
人間の遺伝子にまで
損傷を与える事が分かったの
橋本･アッペルバウム症候群の
典型だったわ
It was a typical case of Hashimoto-Appelbaum syndrome.
橋本･アッペルバウム症候群…
Hashimoto-Appelbaum syndrome…
Unlike Fiends, they use their Cantus subconsciously.
悪鬼と違って
無意識のうちに呪力をふるうの
More accurately, they have no control whatsoever over the dangerous leakage of their Cantus.
というより
その危険な呪力の漏出は
本人にはコントロールできない
This is what changing into a Karma Demon means.
それが
｢業魔化する｣ということなの
業魔化…
A Karma Demon…
Even now it pains me to remember.
今でも心が痛むわ…
Izumi-chan was a kind and gentle girl with every fiber of her being.
泉美ちゃんは 本当に
素直で心の優しい いいコだった
でも過去の例からすると
そういうコの方が
However, as history has shown, those are precisely the ones most in danger of becoming Karma Demons.
むしろ 業魔になる確率が高いのよ
泉美ちゃんは自分のせいで
多くの人の命が
When she learned that she had put the lives of many people in danger, she herself proposed that she be disposed of.
危険にさらされていると知ると
自ら進んで
いかなる処分にも協力することを
申し出た
ちなみにね
彼女には知らせなかったけど
Meanwhile—and we never told her this—her family and the farm workers had already mutated and died.
両親と湫川農場の従業員は
既に奇形化して死んでいたの
We told her it was medicine to stop the bad spill.
バッド･スピルを抑制するための
薬という説明だった
Only one of those pills was lethal.
１つだけ 致死性の薬が入っていた
We told her that taking one each day would cure her.
毎日 一錠ずつ
それを服用するよう指示されたの
でも聡明な彼女は
それに気づいていた
But, being the smart girl that she was, she figured it out.
いいのよ 好きなだけ泣きなさい
It’s okay.
Cry if you need to.
Why…
どうして… どうして
こんなに悲しいんですか？
Why is it so sad?
I cannot answer that yet.
それは まだ言えない
でも 人は大きな悲しみに
直面したとき
But when confronting our grief, we need to give ourselves time to mourn so that we can accept and overcome it.
それを消化し受け入れるための
喪の作業というものが必要なのよ
あなたは こうやって
涙を流す必要があった…
You needed a chance to shed tears.
Is this related to the memories that have been purged from our minds?
それは 私たちの記憶から
消された出来事と
関係があるんですか？
ええ そうよ
Yes, it is.
僕には顔がないんだ
I have no face.
でも 僕の顔なら
君は よく知ってるはずだよ
You should know well what I look like, though.
私の記憶を返してください！
Please give me back my memories!
それは できないわ
We cannot do that.
あのコに関する情報を
抹消することを決めたのは
We resolved to erase all traces of him because the incident was so shocking and visceral.
あれが あまりにも生々しく
衝撃的な事件だったからよ
We were afraid that mere memories of the events would be traumatic,
事件の記憶自体が
トラウマとなって
町の人の精神を不安定化し
destabilizing the minds of the villagers and bringing even greater tragedy upon us.
さらなる悲劇の
呼び水になる恐れさえあった
まるでドミノ倒しのようにね
An insidious domino effect.
あなたなら
それに耐えられるかもしれない
You might be able to endure it.
But if I restore your memory, you won’t be able to keep it a secret from your friends, right?
でも あなたの記憶の封印を解けば
友達に秘密にしておくことは
できないでしょ？
結局は みんなが知ることになる
In the end, everyone would find out.
でも…
But…
Please think about it.
よく考えてみて 鎖は常に
いちばん弱い環から破断するのよ
A chain is only as strong as its weakest link.
私たちは 常に最も弱い者に対して
気を配らなくてはならないの
We must give the most care and attention to the weakest ones.
The weakest ones?
最も弱い者にですか？
さっき あなたに私の後を
継いでもらいたいって言ったのは
When I asked you to succeed me earlier, I was by no means joking.
決して冗談じゃないの
その時が来れば
At that point you would also be allowed to retrieve your lost memories.
あなたは失った記憶を
取り戻すことも許される
There is no way I could ever replace you!
私 富子さんの代わりなんで
絶対 できません！
I understand you well.
気持ちは分かるわ
私も かつて そうだったから
I used to be the same.
But one day there will be a time when you must do what needs to be done.
でも いつか必ず
やらざるを得ないときが来る
それが あなたしかできない
仕事だからよ
It’s a task only you can shoulder.
いい？ そのときに思い出して
Do you understand?
Remember then what we must do to stop Fiends and Karma Demons from appearing again.
２度と再び
悪鬼や業魔を出さないためには
何をしなければならないのか
Don't look for me.
Mamoru
おはようございます
Good morning.
あっ 真理亜ちゃん…
守が… 守が…
Maria-chan!
Mamoru… Mamoru…!
何で突然… 一体… 何が…
Why would he? What happened?
この事は
誰にも言わないでください！
Don't tell anyone about this!
え？
言わないでください！
No one!
どうしよう
What should we do?
決まってるじゃない
捜すしかないわ
Isn't that obvious? We have to look for him!
覚も入れて ３人で守を追うのよ
Let's get Satoru and go.
But wouldn't it be suspicious if everyone from Group One suddenly skipped school?
でも １班の４人が全員休んだら
変に思われるんじゃない？
うん… うん 分かった
That's right. Let's go to school for now.
いったん 登校しよう
３限 ４限目は自由研究じゃない？
We've got independent observation for 3rd and 4th periods, right?
Let's sneak out then.
その時
こっそり学校を出ればいいわ
だけど ホームルームまでに
戻って来るなんて 絶対無理よ
We'll never make it back for homeroom, though.
言い訳は 後から考えよう
Let's think of our excuses afterwards.
This was the first proposal to regulate the ethics of human society.
人間社会における倫理について
初めて提唱されたのが この時です
Clause 39 set the new standard for ethics.
この第39条を ひな形にして
新しい倫理観が…
Independent          Observation
必要なら
校外に出ても かまいませんが
You can leave the school grounds if necessary,
班ごとに
行動するようにしてください
but please do so in your groups.
お～い！ みんな…
どこ 行くんだよ？
Hey! Where are you going, guys?
Don't we have independent observation?
自由研究じゃないか
That's why I'm asking where you're going.
だから どこ行くんだって
聞いてるんだよ
僕も同じ１班だし
I'm in Group One too.
Don't you always hang out with Group Two?
あなた いつも２班の子たちと
一緒にいるじゃない？
でも 一応は１班なんだよ
But officially I'm in Group One.
それに 昔は君らのグループに
Not to mention we used to be together for such a long time.
いただろう？
どうして こんなふうに
It's a mystery to me how this even happened.
なっちゃったのかは
分からないけど…
Right, right. Sorry.
分かった分かった 悪かったよ
まだ説明してなかったな
We never told you, did we?
前の話し合いの時 いなかったよな
You weren't there the last time we met.
…そんで 雪の結晶を
調べようってなったんだ
We decided to research snowflakes.
雪の結晶？
何だよ 子供っぽいなぁ
Snowflakes? But that's for children.
友愛園の時にやったよ
We did that back in Friendship School.
It's no ordinary observation!
ただの観察じゃないって
呪力の作用によって
We want to look into how Cantus can affect them.
どう変化するか調べるんだよ
もう 分担を決めてあるから
We've already decided how to split the work.
Could you look behind the school?
良は校舎の裏を調べてくれ
What am I supposed to do?
何を どうするんだよ？
まず 結晶を虫眼鏡で拡大して
模様を描くんだ
First look at the snowflakes under a
magnifying glass and draw their shape.
最低でも100はいるよな？
We'll need at least a hundred.
Then, after you broadly categorize them by shape,
…んで
それを大まかな形で分類する
最後に いくつかを選んで
一定の場所に積もった雪に
you choose a few and try to copy their pattern to another patch of snow.
呪力で転写できるかどうかを
実験してくれ
But can snowflakes change their shape once they're frozen?
でも すでに出来上がってる
結晶の形が変わるかな？
そう そこだよ！
流石！ いいか？
Yeah, that's the point! You're so sharp!
Most solid objects are some kind of crystal, right?
固体っていうのは
大半が何らかの結晶だろ？
So if we could change the shape of
water crystals without melting them,
だから 水の結晶を溶かす事なく
呪力で変形させられるなら
we could change other objects a lot more freely than we can right now!
ほとんどの固体の物性が
今より ずっと自由自在に
変化させられるかも
しれないじゃないか
ふ～ん…
僕の担当は校舎の裏だな？
So you want me to check behind the school?
Yeah, please.
ああ 頼むぜ
俺らも手分けして調べるから
We're gonna split up to search too.
分かった
Okay.
悪魔
You're so evil.
Come on, it was the best solution.
何だよ しかたないだろ？
一旦 帰って
必要な物 取ってくる！
I'll be right back with some stuff!
Do you have any ideas?
何か心当たりあるの？
Not really. He just looked kinda down lately.
わからない… でも このところ
ちょっと塞ぎ込んでたかも
Did something happen?
何かあったの？
う～ん…
そんな 大した事じゃないんだけど
Well…
It wasn't anything serious…
There was an assignment he couldn't really work out.
課題が うまく
できなかったことがあってね
守の実力なら楽勝のはずだったの
It should've been easy for him.
でも 一度
失敗するんじゃないかって思うと
But once he considers the
possibility of failing, it's all hopeless.
もうだめなのよ
それだけ？
That's all?
No. I think the teacher gave him an earful.
ううん それで先生に
指導されたことを気にしてて…
I joked that they might send a Copycat after him,
ネコダマシが
来るんじゃないかって
冗談っぽく言ってたけど
もう 顔が真っ青で
but he went pale as death and took it really seriously.
全然 冗談と思えないのが
丸 分かりなの
クラスから消えた子たちのこと
We shouldn't have talked about the people who vanished from class…
話したの まずかったかな…
Huh? What?
え？ 何？
鎖は常に
一番弱い環から破断する…
A chain is only as strong as its weakest link.
Huh?
Nakisou na aoringo kakaeteru mune no oku
泣きそうな青リンゴ  抱えてる胸の奥
In my chest, I carry a green apple that wets my eyes
Korogatte tsuyogatte
転がって  強がって
I fall over yet pretend to be strong
Kyuukutsu na sora niramu
窮屈な空睨む
I glower at the sky and it seems to suffocate me
Unmei ni juujun ni
運命に従順に
Do I look like I'd wait quietly
Jukusu no wo matsu mon ka
熟すのを待つもんか
For destiny to ripen it?
Sen no kaze
千の風
The winds
Agaite sakende
あがいて  叫んで
I struggle and scream
Fuke fuke
吹け吹け
Blow and blow
Watashi wa shabondama
わたしはしゃぼん玉
I'm a soap bubble
Soredemo shinjiteru
それでも信じてる
And still I have faith
Yokisenu arashi ni
予期せぬ  嵐に
In a sudden storm
Joushou shite kakou shite
上昇して  下降して
I rise and fall
Aragau shabondama
あらがうしゃぼん玉
I fight, soap bubble that I am
Soredemo ikiteku
それでも生きてく
And still I live on
Hajikeru shunkan niji hanate
弾ける瞬間  虹、放て
I make a rainbow when I burst
FROM
THE
NEW
WORLD
どこ？ 守はどこ？
Where is he?! Where's Mamoru?!
たぶん バケネズミだ
It must be a queerat.
What's it doing here?
こんな所で何してるの？
Hurry! We have to find Mamoru quickly!
早く！
早く 守を捜してあげなくちゃ！
Is someone there?
誰かいるの？
Satoru! Maria!
覚 真理亜… はっ！